>> Computers are now used
everywhere around us.
You will find them
at work, in stores,
in hospitals, and at home.
A computer is an electronic
machine that can process,
store, and retrieve
different types
of data and information.
You can use the
computer to perform
many tasks such as
writing documents,
playing games, sending emails,
learning new skills, browsing
the web, and watching movies.
All computers consists of
two main parts,
hardware and software.
Software refers to the
intangible parts of a computer,
the parts that can't be touched.
This includes
the instructions that
control how the
hardware functions,
the applications running
on the computer,
and the data stored
on the computer.
Hardware includes all of
the physical parts that
make up a computer
such as the monitor and
the central processing unit,
that keeps data moving.
There are various types
of computers
that you may encounter,
but they all share
the same fundamental purpose
of processing and
storing information.